Leon Polk Smith
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Financial Records, 1979-1990, Series 5:; (Box 6; 15 folders)
  - Corporate Taxes, 1986 Preparation and Past Amounts Due, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Corporate Taxes, 1987 Preparation and Past Amounts Due, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Corporate Taxes, 1988 Preparation and Past Amounts Due, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Corporate Taxes, 1989 Preparation and Past Amounts Due, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Taxes, Past Amounts Due, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Personal Taxes, 1987-1989 Filing Forms, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Printed Material, 1941-1997, Series 6:; (Boxes 6-7, 9; .5 linear feet)
  Printed material consists of two books, including the Brooklyn Museum's monograph Leon Polk Smith: American Painter, newspaper clippings reviewing Smith's work, and exhibition announcements and catalogs of Smith's museum and gallery shows from 1941 to 1997.
  The bulk of this series has been scanned. In most cases, only the cover, title page, and individual relevant pages have been scanned from published materials.
  - Book, Design by Paul Zelansky and Mary Fisher, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Book, Leon Polk Smith: American Painter by The Brooklyn Museum, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Clippings, Leon Polk Smith, 1941-1979, (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 35-37)
  - Clippings, Smith's Influences, 1972-1991 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1941-1958, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 39-40)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1969, (Oversized material housed in Box 9, F1) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1971-1985, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 3-5)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1986-1997, (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 6-9)
  - Stedelijk Museum Catalog, Vormen van de Kleur, 1967, (Scanned with Box 7, F2) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook, 1930-1940, Series 7:; (Box 8; 1 folder)
  The scrapbook consists of newspaper clippings documenting Smith's years as an educator and artist in Oklahoma in the 1930s and 1940s.
  - Scrapbook, circa 1930-1940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Photographic Material, 1930-1990, Series 8:; (Box 8; 8 folders)
  Photographic material includes black and white photographs of Smith and his acquaintances circa 1930-1960, and a representative selection of black and white photographs and color slides of Smith's artwork from 1939 to 1960.
  Original photographs have been scanned. Photographs and slides of artwork have not been scanned.
  - Photographs of Leon Polk Smith with Friends and Family, circa 1930-1960, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
  - Photographs of Artwork, 1939-1949, circa 1960-1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Artwork, 1950-1959, circa 1960-1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Artwork, 1960-1979, circa 1960-1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Slides of Artwork, 1937-1969, circa 1960-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Slides of Artwork, 1970-1996, circa 1970-1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)